0xBitcoin is the first fully decentralized ERC20 token
0xBitcoin은 최초로 완전히 탈중앙화된 ERC20 토큰이며,
and is the first purely mined token on Ethereum
이더리움에서 전적으로 채굴된 최초의 토큰입니다.
and it aims to be the primary medium of exchange
또한, 0xBitcoin은 이더리움 네트워크의 주요 교환 수단 및
and store of value on the Ethereum network.
가치 저장 수단이 되는 것을 목표로 합니다.
The 0xBitcoin token was deployed to the Ethereum blockchain in
0xBitcoin 토큰은 2018년 2월 이더리움 블록체인에 배포되었습니다.
February 2018 with the following attributes:
0xBitcoin 토큰의 특징은 다음과 같습니다.
first mineable token,
최초의 채굴 가능한 토큰,
ERC20 compatible,
ERC20과 호환 가능,
no pre-mine or instamine,
사전채굴 또는 인스타마인(Instamine) 없음,
and no ICO.
ICO 없음.
Ether was never intended to act as a currency, and
이더(Ether)는 화폐처럼 작용할 의도가 전혀 없으며,
0xBitcoin will allow Ether to fulfill its sole intended purpose
0xBitcoin은 이더가 이더리움 네트워크를 안전하게 보호하는
of securing the Ethereum network.
고유의 의도한 목적만 수행하도록 할 것입니다.
0xBitcoin takes the best properties of Bitcoin and Ethereum
0xBitcoin은 비트코인과 이더리움의 강점만을 결합해 만든
and combines them into one token.
토큰입니다.
It can be mined exactly like Bitcoin
비트코인과 마찬가지로 채굴할 수 있지만
but transferred 10 times faster and 100 times cheaper.
10배 더 빠르게, 100배 더 저렴하게 전송됩니다.
0xBitcoin combines the Bitcoin properties of
0xBitcoin은
block rewards, proof-of-work issuance,
블록 보상, 작업증명 발급 및 2천 1백만 코인 총액의 비트코인 특징과
and a 21 million coin cap
속도, 디앱, 탈중앙거래소 거래와 같은
with the Ethereum properties of
이더리움 특징을
speed, DApps, and DEX trading.
갖추었습니다.
And unlike Ether, it interfaces with smart contracts
또한, 0xBitcoin은 이더와 달리
for storing and transferring value.
가치 저장 및 전송을 위해 스마트 계약과 연동됩니다.
While Bitcoin can only be traded using centralized means,
비트코인은 중앙화된 방법으로만 거래할 수 있는 반면,
0xBitcoin can be traded permissionlessly via
0xBitcoin은 중앙화된 단체가
smart contracts which cannot be affected or controlled
영향을 미치거나 제약할 수 없는 스마트 계약을
by central entities.
통해 무허가로 거래됩니다.
It is also immune to 51% attacks.
51%의 공격에도 영향을 받지 않습니다.
Add all this to the proven market demand for a
라이트코인(Litecoin)의 성공에서 본 것처럼
faster version of Bitcoin, as we've seen in
더 견고한 비트코인 버전을 바라는 시장의 검증된 요구에 이 모든 특징을 더한다면,
Litecoin's success, and it is plain that
0xBitcoin은 분명히
0xBitcoin fills a hole in the crypto market space.
암호화폐 시장의 부족한 부분을 채울 것입니다.
People are excited about the project in no small part due to
사람들은
the decentralization of the token
토큰의 탈중앙화와
and the active and engaged community
토큰으로 인해 형성된 활발하고 적극적인 커뮤니티
which has sprung up around the token.
덕분에 프로젝트에 대해 크게 기대하고 있습니다.
The community has achieved several key milestones
프로젝트가 시작된 이래
since the project's launch, including
커뮤니티는 라바 지갑의 지속적인 개발, 채석 및 오프체인(off-chain) 거래뿐만 아니라
creating an EIP specifically for mineable tokens,
채굴 가능한 토큰을 위한 구체적인 EIP 생성,
creation of mining pools with multiple new mining clients,
다수의 새로운 채굴 클라이언트를 가진 마이닝 풀의 생성과 같은
as well as ongoing development of Lava Wallet,
몇 가지 중요한
Quarry, and off-chain transactions.
이정표를 세웠습니다.
0xBitcoin is a unique project, backed by a passionate community
0xBitcoin은
dedicated to making it the primary transfer of value
0xBitcoin을 이더리움 네트워크의 주요 가치 전송 수단으로 만들기 위해
for the Ethereum network.
헌신하는 열정적인 커뮤니티가 지원하는 특별한 프로젝트입니다.